We should organize and
host an eating contest.
Allow me to explain.
Now that we've dealt with Chain
Restaurant's fake Boxo scheme,
and with the walls around the village set
to be completely fixed
in the next two weeks,
I predict we'll have a
large influx of people
coming to visit the
Clearflow Lake Stratum.
That's why...
The restaurant union should put
on a big event to attract new
customers under the guise of
celebrating the wall's completion.
Gotcha.
That's why she suggested
an eating contest.
Great idea.
Hunters love food and they
can really pack it in.
We could have a grand
prize for the winner.
That way it'll drum up more excitement.
And with a small admission fee, we'll
be able to easily cover the overhead.
We have to make sure whatever we
serve is as filling as possible.
Let's aim to have the event in two weeks.
We'll put up leaflets all around town and
get everybody talking about the contest!
I'm glad they figured it out,
but did I need to be here?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
How can I not know?
I can't understand that.
I'm a kid. I'm a kid.
I'm a kid.
Please, Mr.
Boxo, if you don't help
us, then we're done for.
What's going on?
You can't ambush Boxo like that.
I don't see why you'd need
his help in the first place.
I thought you had the eating
contest handled already.
Yeah, same here.
I even plan on competing. We did.
It's true that everything was going well.
That is, until we found out
that they were entering.
Who are they?
Walking disasters.
The veins of eating competitions!
Shwee, the inhaler, and the band of
gluttons have officially signed up!
Your stomach's like a bottomless pit.
I'm impressed.
Oh, I'm just getting started. Trust me.
Oh, wow.
It'd be bad enough if it was just a band
of gluttons, but shwees joining in, too?
I can't figure out how they can
fit that much in their bellies.
If we have to feed them all, we're
going to go way into the red!
Is it even possible to get that much food?
We worked as hard as we could
to make this event a success,
but everything we did
was completely pointless!
So you're trying to figure out how to fill
up those bottomless
pits they call stomachs.
Do you have any items
that could help them out?
Oh, I think I've had one of these before.
It's a sweet drink that
bubbles in your mouth.
They can be pretty filling, too.
Are you suggesting we provide
this to contestants during
the competition so they
fill up faster and eat less?
Hello there.
That could work. Wait a sec.
If this drink is more filling than water,
I wonder if people
would complain about it.
That's a good point.
I know I'd have a problem with it.
Perhaps we could let them choose
which beverage they'd like to drink.
Doesn't that give those who
pick water an advantage?
Who would choose water
over this tasty drink?
Alright, how about this?
For now, let's advertise this drink
while increasing its price. Then,
we'll spread the word that
participants can drink
as much of it as they
want during the contest.
That's a good idea.
No one would pass up the
chance to drink it then.
Please, Mr. Boxo!
If you could find it in your heart to
sell us this drink at a reasonable price,
we'd be in your debt!
Hello there.
I knew we could count on you, Boxo.
Do you think you could stick around the
contest to make sure it all goes smoothly?
Hello there.
Look at that crowd.
We need more meat.
Hurry up.
We got a fresh delivery from
some hunters in the storeroom.
I know better than to ask
what kind of meat it is.
Ladies and gentlemen, thank
you so much for waiting.
On behalf of the restaurant union,
we'd like to welcome you to the Clear
Flow Lake Stratum's first eating contest.
We've got more entries than we expected.
So, after a short elimination round,
we've sorted the remaining
contestants into two separate blocks.
The best five eaters from each group
will then advance to the finals.
We've prepared an incredible
grand prize for today's champion.
We wish you the best of luck.
Now, could all competitors
in Block 1 come on stage?
Please, all Block 1 eaters.
You have until the very last grain of
sand falls to the bottom of the hourglass.
Contestants must finish
all the food on their
plate before time is
up in order to advance.
Right, you have to eat fast, too.
As long as there aren't
any other questions,
we're going to kick off
this eating contest.
Get ready, set, eat!
Can I get second?
I cleaned my plane. Me too.
I'm finished over here as well.
Four contestants have finished already.
It's a race for Block One's last spot.
I believe that honor belongs to me.
There you have it, folks.
These five have qualified
before the time limit. Damn it.
They're all monsters.
Whoa, Goat Guy's the only human in
block one to move up to the finals.
The band of gluttons are amazing.
Thanks for participating.
You can take home any leftovers.
Alrighty then, it's
time for us to move on.
Would all contestants in block two
please make your way to the stage.
I'm rooting for you, Miss Shirley!
Woo-hoo!
It's surprising to see Shirley here.
I would have never expected
that she was a big eater.
I hope everyone in block two is hungry.
Get ready, set, eat!
I looked away for a second, and
she'd already cleaned her plate.
Seems I'm the first one to finish.
That was tasty.
I suppose I'll be moving on as well.
Count me in, too.
I just finished eating.
It was so good!
And that's time!
Utensils down!
With that, we've determined
our top ten finalists.
The finals will take place in two hours.
Meanwhile, we've brought in a
theater troupe to entertain you.
And of course, we hope you'll sample some
of our delicious offerings while you wait.
Oh!
I thought you'd set up outside.
This is great I was feeling thirsty
ah so the troop is putting on a play
the Farm that calls happiness huh
I've never heard of it oh it's time
That was actually pretty good uh-huh
can't say I expected that Wow I didn't See
that twist coming at all hey Lamas don't
you have the finals oh I forgot All right,
let's go.
Hello there.
Good luck, guys.
Are you ready?
Welcome to the eating contest finals.
Contestants to the stage.
Huh? Music?
This is a new function
I gained at rank two.
I figured I could liven things up with it.
Is the band hidden somewhere?
Anyway, I hope everybody's
having a great time.
For the finals,
whoever eats the most within the time
limit will be crowned the champion.
I wish all LARC finalists
the best of luck.
Get ready, set, eat!
I'm holding for you, shut up now!
Come on, band of buttons!
Wow!
They brought out a new dish!
They're huge!
Those are crepes,
mercilessly stuffed with all kinds
of fruits and other ingredients.
The fruit filling was
provided by yours truly.
Oh, that's a sweet dish.
It looks super tasty.
I'd love to try one of those.
She's making that big
fruit thingy look amazing.
This is making me feel
hungry now, dang it.
Whoa, get a load of Suco!
She's crushing plate after plate!
This is coming down to a
duel between her and Shui!
I managed to finish it all!
I knew you could pull it off, little girl!
I can't believe she
beat the band of glums!
Congrats!
It's too bad that Goat Guy
didn't really stand out.
But he did a lot better than I expected.
Don't look so disappointed.
You see, the grand prize
for today's winner is Boxxo.
You can use him for free for one day.
What?
Boxxo, please say it's okay.
You did tell us that we could come to
you if we needed any help after all.
Oh.
Well, I've made a decent number of points
selling cola, and I did promise I'd help.
If it's just one day, I should be fine.
Check it out, guys.
I won the eating competition,
so Boxo belongs to me today.
You're so lucky, Shui.
I wish I could have Boxo.
Wow, you can pretty much eat
and drink as much as you want.
That was some good eating, Shui.
Since we've got Boxo here,
this is the perfect chance.
To go monster hunting we could
use some more funds good idea huh?
Stop trying to take him away from me.
I won box of ferrian square he's mine
you hear plus we already have plans
we're going on a date to the origin
stratum what's the origin stratum?
I haven't been here in
forever so many memories.
Truthfully i actually
come here fairly often.
I didn't know you were gonna
take him to the first stratum.
Well in that case go on ahead
you've got better things to do.
What did the captain mean by that?
Is there something special here?
Hey Shui where are we headed to?
It's just a bit further.
We
finally made it.
Hello is anyone there?
I'm back for a visit.
Hey look it's Shui.
I think Sister Shui came
back to see us. I heard.
Everyone's so excited.
It's good to see you. Welcome home.
It's great to be back, Madam Director?
Is that a new friend of
yours standing behind you?
Something like that.
We adventure together!
Nice to meet you, I promise.
It's wonderful to meet a friend of Shui's?
Why don't we continue our
talk inside the house?
Please, come on in.
Sure!
Thank you, ma 'am.
Will the floor even hold
your weight? Too bad.
It may not seem like it, but this
box is actually a magical item.
If you press on it here, it'll
give you some tasty stuff. Really?
If you want a recommendation,
this brown stuff is delicious.
What about that one?
That's a crunchy snack.
It's salty but really good.
If you put all these
cute kids in front of me,
I don't have a choice but
to give stuff out for free.
Any vending machine would do the same.
Why is the box glowing like that?
It's a wall!
All right, here you go.
Wow, thank you!
I love it! Amazing!
But wait, that's not all.
You guys ready?
Here it comes!
Everyone, when you're done, go ahead
and put your wet clothes in here.
Yes, ma 'am!
Whoa, look at that.
It's washing all our clothes. Well,
I never expected Boxo could do the laundry,
Magic items these days sure are handy.
Let's go take a bath.
He should be done washing
everything by the time we get out.
Aww.
You guys better make it snappy, or
the licking monster will catch you!
Don't run away from you!
What are we gonna do?
There's no hot water in the bath.
Goodness, that's certainly not ideal.
Who was supposed to be on bath duty today?
We're really sorry about this, ma 'am.
We were having so much
fun playing with you.
Shibby, we totally forgot.
I see now.
It's good you told me.
Thank you, girls.
Remember, everybody makes mistakes,
but we shouldn't cover it up.
Instead, we should always take
responsibility for them and learn from it.
Okay.
By the time we gather the water and
wood to heat it up, it'll be too late.
Why don't we skip the baths for today?
We'll make sure we wash
up properly tomorrow.
Huh? Voxo?
What's going on?
I've never seen that before.
Behold, my fourth form change of the day.
I've turned into a hot
spring vending machine.
What are you planning?
Is something supposed to
come out of this hose?
Whoa, look at it go!
The tub is full of water already!
Waxo is amazing!
Let's go!
Hey, wait for me!
Stop!
Don't run, you guys!
Thank you, Boxo.
We appreciate everything
you've done for us.
Hello there.
To be honest with you,
whenever Shui would come home, it seemed
like she was worried about something.
It's a relief to see her
so happy and relaxed.
That's in no small part thanks to you.
I hope you'll continue to look after her.
Hello there.
I might as well give them a couple
extra sets of clothes and towels, too.
Hold on.
Maybe I'm overthinking it, but am I
just teaching them to expect handouts?
I'm never sure how involved I
should get in these situations.
Hey, Foxo, your lights started flickering.
You weren't thinking about
something weird again, were you?
Aw, crap.
Apparently I do that involuntarily
when I'm lost in thought.
You really should have more confidence.
Everyone here is smiling
because of all the good food.
And that's thanks to you. So be happy.
Lamas is amazing.
She can tell what a vending
machine like me is feeling,
and then she knows the
perfect thing to say.
Every day I count my lucky stars
it was Lamas who first found me.
We're in a cave where you
can't even see the sky.
It's nearly impossible to
tell morning from night.
Boxo, thanks for everything
that you did today.
It's been a while since
I've seen everyone so happy.
Thank you very much!
Giving all that away
must have been pricey.
I'll make it up to you, I swear.
I just need a little time.
Too bad. Huh?
Oh, you want your money now, too bad?
Thank you very much.
Wait, what do you mean?
Are you saying I don't
need to pay you back?
Hello there!
I was kind of thirsty,
so this is perfect.
Wait, don't chug it like that.
You could even win a reward.
Anyway, this is your
first time here, right?
Did you know everyone entering the dungeon
has to pass through the origin stratum?
Too bad to get to the other strata?
Adventurers have to make their
way through this stratum first,
and then they take the
transfer circle out.
It's a test.
If somebody can't handle the journey through
the origin stratum, then it's a sign?
and they have no business trying
to go deeper into the dungeon.
Hold on.
You're saying that all
the non-hunters I've met
so far have had to make
their way through this place?
But because of that, there are a
lot of people left in the stratum?
who, for whatever reason, never
made it to the transfer circle.
This is where the children
who were abandoned gather,
stuck in a place where they
can't even see the sun?
or feel the wind on their faces.
They're trapped here.
All I want is for the children
in this stratum to be happy.
Sorry.
For some reason, I've been
a real blabbermouth today.
Forget everything I
said, okay? It's bedtime!
I'll see you tomorrow!
So where is this place?
We're almost there, boss.
Heard they've got some
kind of special magic item.
It's been a while since
anyone's tried to steal me.
I guess I should have expected this
since this area isn't exactly safe.
You're saying this giant box
spits out as much food as we want?
I saw it with my own eyes, sir.
What should I do here?
I could wake up Lamas and
Shwee with a loud noise.
But if things go south, the kids
could be put into harm's way.
All right.
I hope you jerks are ready for this
week's vending machine surprise.
The hell?
Where's the smoke coming from?
Also, is anyone else hearing that?
Yeah, it kind of sounds like flowing water
and howling wind, but that can be like...
What are you talking about?
There aren't any rivers
or springs around here.
You must be imagining things.
And finally, the burial.
Run, dammit!
We gotta get the hell out of here!
Please wait for us, boss.
Too bad.
I look forward to serving you again.
Did this really happen
while we were sleeping?
I recognize them.
They're a couple of former
hunters who set up a base nearby.
So they turn to a life of crime.
Such naughty boys.
All right.
I'll be heading out for a while.
Can you two look after
the children for me?
Yes, ma 'am.
It's been forever since I've seen
her actually get mad like this.
Madam Director's the person
who taught me archery.
She used to be a hunter.
Apparently she and Director Bear used
to go raiding together all the time.
Even Captain Kerioyl admits
she's a lot better than him.
Oh, I didn't know that.
About an hour later, she returned
with a big smile on her face.
Everything's fine.
I gave them a stern talking to, and they
were more than happy to listen to reason.
They promised that they'd never
try to meddle with you again.
I'm pretty sure that quiver was full
of arrows when she left earlier.
Thank you very much.
That's Shwee's teacher for you.
Hold on a second.
Does that mean Shwee's gonna grow up
to be like Madam Director one day?
Something wrong?
Too bad
I'll
I love you, but I'm
happy with this moment.
Today is a day for a
day, always for a soup.
I look forward to serving you again.